Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Museum, Getty Villa Construction Records, 1960, 1964, 1968-1986 and undated (bulk 1971-1974) IA10001
Institutional Records and Archives
- Dinwiddie Construction Company records, 1970-1975; Series V.; 6.9 Linear Feet (18.5 boxes)
  - Budgets and billings, 1970-1975; Series V.C.; 6.25 Linear Feet (15 boxes)
    - Dinwiddie/Subcontractor billing and payroll:
      - December 1971, [Files 2-3] (Box 1986.IA.08-17, Folder 1-2)
      - January 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-17, Folder 3-5)
      - February 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-17, Folder 6-8)
      - March 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-18, Folder 1-3)
      - April 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-18, Folder 4-6)
      - May 1972, [Files 1-2 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-18, Folder 7-8)
      - May 1972, [File 3 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-19, Folder 1)
      - June 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-19, Folder 2-4)
      - July 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-19, Folder 5-7)
      - August 1972, [File 1 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-19, Folder 8)
      - August 1972, [Files 2-3] (Box 1986.IA.08-20, Folder 1-2)
      - September 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-20, Folder 3-5)
      - October 1972, [Files 1-2 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-20, Folder 6-7)
      - October 1972, [File 3 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-21, Folder 1)
      - November 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-21, Folder 2-4)
      - December 1972, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-21, Folder 5-7)
      - January 1973, [File 1 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-21, Folder 8)
      - January 1973, [Files 2-3] (Box 1986.IA.08-22, Folder 1-2)
      - February 1973, [3-files] (Box 1986.IA.08-22, Folder 3-5)
      - March 1973, [Files 1-2 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-22, Folder 6-7)
      - March 1973, [File 3 of 3] (Box 1986.IA.08-23, Folder 1)
      - April 1973, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-23, Folder 2-4)
      - May 1973, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-23, Folder 5-7)
      - June 1973, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-24, Folder 1-3)
      - July 1973, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-24, Folder 4-6)
      - August 1973, [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-25, Folder 1-4)
      - September 1973, [Files 1-3 of 4] (Box 1986.IA.08-25, Folder 5-7)
      - September 1973, [File 4 of 4] (Box 1986.IA.08-26, Folder 1)
      - October 1973, [4 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-26, Folder 2-5)
      - December 1973, [Files 1-3 of 7] (Box 1986.IA.08-26, Folder 6-8)
      - December 1973, [Files 4-7] (Box 1986.IA.08-27, Folder 1-4)
      - January 1974, [3 files] (Box 1986.IA.08-27, Folder 5)
      - February-March 1974, [File 1 of 4] (Box 1986.IA.08-27, Folder 8)
      - February-March 1974, [Files 2-4] (Box 1986.IA.08-28, Folder 1-3)
      - June 1974, [2 folders] (Box 1986.IA.08-28, Folder 4-5)
      - May 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-28, Folder 6)
      - September 1974 (Box 1986.IA.08-28, Folder 7)
- Blueline prints and architectural drawings, 1964; 1968,; 1970-1977,; undated; Series VI.; 22.4 Linear Feet (1 box, 6 flat file drawers, 2 oversize boxes)
  Materials produced by Langdon & Wilson precede those produced by other sources. In each case, the blueline drawings are followed by drawings and photographs of the blueline drawings. The Langdon & Wilson blueline drawings are listed in the order which they appear in the index found in the first folder.
  Records consist of blueline drawings, color pencil, ink, and watercolor drawings, memoranda, photographs, negatives, transparencies, and an index, dating 1964, 1968, 1970-1977, and undated, created for the J. Paul Getty Museum (Villa) construction project by Langdon & Wilson, the primary architects, and by Stephen Garrett, John S. Gregory Co, Emmet Wemple, Garth Benton, and David Wilkins. The drawings were used to describe, in technical detail, various aspect of the Villa building, from the overall site plan to cross-sectional views and to details of both mosaic floors and plumbing schematics. The dates listed for the drawings reflect the earliest date on each drawing, though some drawings do contain later additions and revisions. The Langdon & Wilson materials include an index of the blueline drawings prepared by the architects. Comparing the blueline drawings listed below with the drawings listed in the index, it does not appear that the existing drawings are a complete set of building plans.
  The color drawings provide representational views of the intended completed Villa building. The photographic media frequently contain images of both the color drawings and the blueline drawings
  - Langdon and Wilson
    - Index to list of Langdon and Wilson drawings, undated (Box 1986.IA.08-28, Folder 8)
    - Langdon and Wilson and Stephen Garrett drawing transmittal sheets, 1971-1973; 1977 (Box 1986.IA.08-28, Folder 9)
    - Negative prints of architectural drawings, October 1968; [15 negatives] (Box 1986.IA.08, Folder 10)
    - Blueline drawings
      - Group 1 - principal contract documents:
        [List of the drawings prepared by the architect and his consultants for the various divisions of the work.]
        - Site Plan, April 16, 1971; 1.0:; [6 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-20)
        - Parking Structure Floor Plan – South Part, April 16, 1971; undated; 1.1 and 2:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-20)
        - Parking Structure Floor Plan – North Part and Entrance, Details, April 16, 1971; undated; 1.2 and 3:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-20)
        - Peristyle Floor Plan – South Part, April 16, 1971; undated; 1.3 and 4:; [4 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-21)
        - Peristyle Floor Plan – North Part, April 16, 1971; undated; 1.4 and 5:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-21)
        - Peristyle Roof Plan – South Part and Roof Details, April 16, 1971; undated; 1.5 and 6:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-21)
        - Peristyle Roof Plan – North Part, April 16, 1971; undated; 1.6 and 7:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-21)
        - Elevations and Sections – Bridge and Peristyle and Part Elevation – East Retaining Wall, April 16, 1971; 2.1:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-22)
        - East and West Elevations – Peristyle and Parking Structure, April 16, 1971; 2.2:; [1 copy] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-22)
        - Parking Structure and Peristyle and Section "A" and Details, April 16, 1971; undated; 3.1 and 8:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-22)
        - Peristyle and Parking Structure Sections, April 16, 1971; undated; 3.2 and 9:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-22)
        - Parking Structure and Peristyle – Detail Plans and Sections, April 16, 1971; 4.1:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-23)
        - Exterior Details, April 16, 1971; 4.2:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-23)
        - Interiors – Stair No. 12 and Elevator Lobby, April 16, 1971; 4.4:; [1 copy] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-23)
        - East and West Terminals – South Bridge, April 16, 1971; 4.8: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-23)
        - Finish Schedule, Door Schedule and Details, April 16, 1971; 5.1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-23)
        - Interior Details – Toilet Rooms, April 16, 1971; 6.1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-23)
        - Museum Basement Plan, August 27, 1971; undated; 1.20:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-24)
        - Museum Main Floor Plan, August 27, 1971; 1.21:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-24)
        - Museum main floor plan, October 23-November 25, 1970 (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-24)
        - Museum Upper Floor Plan, August 27, 1971; 1.22:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-24)
        - Museum Roof Plan, August 27, 1971; 1.23:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-25)
        - Museum Basement – Ceiling Plan, undated; 1.24: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-25)
        - Museum Upper Floor – Ceiling Plan, undated; 1.26: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-25)
        - East, South and West Exterior Elevations, August 27, 1971; 2.20:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-26)
        - North Exterior Elevation and Building Sections, August 27, 1971; 3.20:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-26)
        - Building Sections, August 27, 1971; 3.21: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-26)
        - West Garden Elevations and Sections, November 12, 1971; 3.22: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-26)
        - North Bridge Plans, Elevations, Sections and Details, November 13, 1971; 3.25: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-26)
        - Entrance Structure (Gate House), June 7, 1973; 3.26: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-26)
        - Half Plan – South Porch of Museum, April 16, 1971; 4.20:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-27)
        - Basement Core Plan, Elevations and Details, November 6, 1971; 4.21: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-27)
        - Main Floor and Upper Floor Toilets and Private Kitchen, November 6, 1971; 4.22: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-27)
        - Miscellaneous Details, December 22, 1971; 4.23: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-27)
        - Wall Sections, November 6, 1971; 4.25:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-27)
        - Wall Sections, November 6, 1971; 4.26: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-28)
        - Wall Sections, November 6, 1971; 4.27: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-28)
        - Exterior Details, June 29, 1972; 4.29: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-28)
        - Details – Entrance Structure (Gate House), June 7, 1973; 4.33: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-28)
        - Museum Door Schedule, July 27, 1971; 5.20:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-28)
        - Typical Details and General Notes, undated; S-1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-29)
          [Superceded by S-1.0.]
        - Typical Details and General Notes, April 16, 1971; S-1.0:; [7 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-29)
        - Parking Structure South Portion – Plan and Foundation Plan, undated; S-2: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-29)
          [Superceded by S-1.1.]
        - Parking Structure South Portion – Plan and Foundation Plan, April 16, 1971; S-1.1:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-29)
        - Parking Structure North Portion – Plan and Foundation Plan, undated; S-3: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-29)
          [Superceded by S-1.2.]
        - Parking Structure North Portion – Plan and Foundation Plan, April 16, 1971; S-1.2: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-29)
        - Peristyle South Portion – Plan, undated; S-4: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-30)
          [Superceded by S-1.3.]
        - Peristyle South Portion – Plan, April 16, 1971; S-1.3:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-30)
        - Peristyle North Portion – Plan, undated; S-5: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-30)
          [Superceded by S-1.4.]
        - Peristyle North Portion – Plan, April 16, 1971; S-1.4: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-30)
        - Peristyle Roof Plan, April 16, 1971; S-1.5: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-30)
        - Museum Foundation and Basement Plan, August 27, 1971; S-1.20:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-31)
        - Museum Main Floor Framing and West Garden Plans, August 27, 1971; S-1.21:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-31)
        - Museum Upper Floor Framing Plan, August 27, 1971; S-1.22:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-31)
        - Museum Roof Framing Plan, August 27, 1971; S-1.23:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-31)
        - Parking Structure and South Bridge – Elevations and Details, April 16, 1971; S-2.1:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-32)
          [One sheet is unnumbered, untitled, and undated.]
        - Parking Structure and Elevations, April 16, 1971; S-2.2:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-32)
        - Museum Wall Elevations and Roof Sections, December 27, 1971; S-2.10: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-32)
        - Parking Structure and Peristyle – Detail Sections, April 16, 1971; S-3.1:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-32)
        - Parking Structure Details, April 16, 1971; S-3.2:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-32)
        - Museum Foundation and Basement Plan, August 27, 1971; S-3.20:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - Museum Main Floor Framing and West Garden Plans, August 27, 1971; S-3.21:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - Museum Upper Floor Framing Plan, December 3, 1971; S-3.22: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - West Garden Plan, Section and Details, May 15, 1972; S-3.24: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - South Bridge Section and Details, [August 1, 1972]; S-3.25: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - North Bridge Section and Details, November 21, 1972; S-3.26: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - South Bridge East and West Terminals, January 8, 1973; S-3.28: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - Entrance Structure (Gate House), March 14, 1973; S-3.30: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - Stair Sections and Details, April 16, 1971; S-4.2:; [5 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-33)
        - Parking Structure – Column and Footing Schedule, April 16, 1971; S-5.1:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-34)
        - Parking Structure Joist and Beam Schedule, April 16, 1971; S-5.2:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-34)
        - Museum Beam Schedule, April 16, 1971; August 27, 1971; S-5.3:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-34)
        - Museum Beam Schedule, August 27, 1971; S-5.4:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-34)
        - Museum Beam Schedule, December 3, 1971; S-5.5: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-34)
        - Electrical Plot Plan, April 16, 1971; E-1.0:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
          [One sheet is unnumbered and undated.]
        - Parking Structure – South Portion Lighting Plan, April 16, 1971; E-1.1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Parking Structure – North Portion Lighting Plan, April 16, 1971; E-1.2: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - East Garden and Entrance Structure Power and Lighting, Plans, February 9, 1973; E-4.13: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Basement Conduit Plan, December 16, 1971; EC-1.20: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Peristyle – North Portion – Lighting Plan, undated; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Peristyle – South Portion – Lighting Plan, undated; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Museum – Ground Floor Lighting Plan, undated; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Museum – Basement Signal and Power Plan, undated; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Museum – Basement Lighting Plan, undated; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-35)
        - Parking Structure Ventilation Plan – South Part, April 16, 1971; undated; AC-1.1 and unnumbered:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Parking Structure Ventilation Plan – North Part, April 16, 1971; undated; AC-1.2 and unnumbered:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Climate Control Schedules, undated; CC-1.0: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Climate Control – Basement Floor Plan, undated; CC-1.20: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Basement Mechanical Equipment Plan and Sections, undated; CC-4.2: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - New Water Distribution Site Plan, June 15, 1971; P-0.0: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Partial Plumbing Site Plan, April 16, 1971; undated; P-1.0 and P-1:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Plumbing Floor Parking Structure – South Part, April 16, 1971; undated; P-1.1 and P-2:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Plumbing Floor Parking Structure – North Part, April 16, 1971; P-1.2 and P-3:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-36)
        - Plumbing Peristyle Floor Plan – South Part, April 16, 1971; P-1.3:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Plumbing Basement Floor Plan, August 27, 1971; P-1.20:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Plumbing Main Floor and East Garden Floor Plan, August 27, 1971; P-1.21:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Plumbing Upper Floor Plan, August 27, 1971; P-1.22:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Plumbing West Garden and West Garden Roof Plans, undated; P-1.23: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Partial Plumbing Plan - Toilet Details, before December 27, 1971; P-4.20: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Waste and Vent Riser Diagrams, undated; P-4.21: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-37)
        - Site Preparation and Study, October 28, 1970; December 3, 1970,; undated; C-1 and B:; [5 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-38)
        - North Access Road – Plan, November 1, 1972; December 7, 1972; C-1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-38)
        - Site Preparation and Excavation, October 28, 1970; December 3, 1970,; undated; C-2 and A:; [5 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-38)
        - Site Preparation and Excavation Profiles and Sections, October 28, 1970; December 3, 1970; C-3:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-38)
        - Sewer and Storm Drain Plan – Lower Portion, July 14, 1971; undated; C-1.1, 1.5, and unnumbered:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Sewer and Drain Plan – Upper Portion, July 24, 1971; C-2.1 and C:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Garage – Museum Local Drainage System, April 10, 1972; C-2.1A: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - City of Los Angeles, Department of Building and Safety, General Grading Requirements, [1973?] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - East Road Plan and Profile, October 30, 1972; C-3.1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Driveway Plan and Profile – South from Garage, May 10, 1972; C-3.1A: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
          [Also contains SS-188, dated July 12, 1973.]
        - South Road Plan and Profile, April 13, 1973; C-3.2:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Sewer and Storm Drain Profile – Lower Portion, October 28, 1971; C-4: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Sewer and Storm Drain Profile – Upper Portion, October 28, 1971; C-4.1: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Storm Drain and Grading Plan – Lower Portion, December 20, 1971; C-4.2: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-39)
        - Landscape – Site Development Work Plan, undated; L-1.0:; [5 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-40)
        - Jute Matting Plan, July 21, 1972; L-1.01: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-40)
        - Phase 5 Work - North Section Site Planting Plan, August 21, 1973; L-1.02:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-40)
        - Perimeter Planting Plan, undated; L-1.02A: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-40)
        - Landscape Plan and Phase 6 Work, November 5, 1973; undated; L-1.04 and unnumbered:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-40)
        - Main Peristyle Planting Plan and Peristyle Garden Site Work and Paving Plan, December 7, 1970; June 29, 1972; L-1.2:; [3 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Miscellaneous Details, July 18, 1973; L-2.3: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Phase 5 Work – Plant List, August 1, 1973; L-2.4: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Miscellaneous Details, July 26, 1973; L-2.5: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Peristyle pool, fountains, grates, retaining wall, and other details (stapled set), 1972-1973 (Box 2013.IA.35-1)
      - Group 2: Services Sheets and Supplemental Architectural Drawings
        [List of those drawings provided for construction to amplify, clarify, modify, or add to work on Group 1 drawings. Service Sheet numbers were assigned chronologically among the architect and his consultants, thus the numbers in any single division are not necessarily in sequence.]
        - Separation Joints in South Bridge above Transformer Vault and Switchgear Room, September 14, 1971; SS-16: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Details – Gallery 128 – Apse Framing and Dome, June 18, 1973; SS-174: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Top of Curb Elevations for Staking Gate House, July 12, 1973; SS-188: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
          [A second copy appears with C-3.1A.]
        - Details – Vestibule 201 – Ceiling, September 10, 1973; SS-193: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
        - Section – Grading at West Terminal of South Bridge, June 28, 1973; [A, SS-L-A?]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-41)
      - Group 3: Preliminary Architectural Drawings
        [List of those drawings provided for the owner's approval, contractor's estimates, and/or preparatory for working drawings.]
        - SK-1 Floor Plan – Garage, October 23, 1970; [III-13]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - SK-2 Floor Plan – Peristyle, October 23, 1970; [III-14]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - SK-3 South Elevation – Peristyle and South Bridge, October 23, 1970; [III-16]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - South End Elevation Garage, October 30, 1970; SK-3 revised: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - SK-3A East Elevation – Parking Structure and Peristyle, October 30, 1970; [III-18]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - SK-4 Main Floor Plan – Museum and Nymphaeum, October 23, 1970; [III-19]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - SK-5 Upper Floor Plan – Museum and Nymphaeum, October 23, 1970; December 3, 1970; [III-20]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-42)
        - SK-6 Basement Plan – Museum, October 23, 1970; [III-21]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - SK-6B Basement Plan – Museum Revised, November 20, 1970; [III-22]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - SK-7 East Elevation – Nymphaeum, October 23, 1970; [III-24]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - East – West Section Thru Center Line Looking South – Nymphaeum, October 23, 1970; [III-25?]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - SK-9 Longitudinal Section –Garage and Peristyle, October 30, 1970; [III-26]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - North – South Cross Section Looking West, October 23, 1970; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - North – South Cross Section Looking East, October 23, 1970; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - North – South Cross Section Looking West, October 23, 1970; [unnumbered]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-43)
        - Studies – Peristyle Paving (Hercules Gallery), December 7, 1970; [unnumbered, III-50A?]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - 2.x Elevations and Sections of Entire Building, August 30, 1971; [III-98]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - On a single sheet: M*1, M*2, M*3, M*4 - Gallery 128 Hall of Cybele, Gallery 129 Hall of Roman Portraits, South Vestibule 101, East Vestibule 122, undated; [III-99, III-100, III-101, III-102]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - M*4 East Vestibule 122, [before June 18, 1971]; [III-102?]:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - M*5 Atrium Gallery 136, Alcoves 136N and S, Vestibule 135, [before June 18, 1971]; [III-103?]:; [2 sheets] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - M*6 Hercules Shrine Gallery 126, undated; [III-104]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - –1.2 Design for Mosaic Fountain, East Wall of East Garden, January 17, 1972; [III-125]: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - On a single sheet - East Terminal of South Bridge, Site Plans of Entrance Area, June 20, 1973; September 8, 1972; III-129A, III-134: (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - Basement Floor Plan, Main Floor Plan, Upper Floor Plan, Roof Plan, October 1972; undated; [unnumbered]:; [2 sheets of 4 pages] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
        - Unfinished blueline drawing, August 15, 1973; [unnumbered]:; [2 sheets of 1] (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-44)
    - Drawings
      - Ink and watercolor drawing of South Facade: Scheme A, mounted, August 9, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-45)
      - Ink and watercolor drawing of South Facade: Scheme B, mounted, August 9, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.19-45)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing of South Facade (as above): Scheme A, August 9, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-3)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing of South Facade (as above): Scheme B, August 9, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-3)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing of aerial view of museum layout and environs: Scheme A, August 9, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-3)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing of aerial view of museum layout and environs: Scheme B, August 9, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-3)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing: Plan of Colonnade Galleries, mounted, October 18, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-4)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing: Plan of Upper Galleries and Courtyard, mounted, October 18, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-4)
      - Blueline drawing and colored pencil drawing: South Facade/North Facade/Transverse Section Looking North/Longitudinal Section Looking East, mounted, October 18, 1968 (Flatfile 1986.IA.36-5)
      - Reproduction of a Langdon and Wilson drawing of exterior view of Museum and environs, on heavy board, unsigned, undated (Box 1986.IA.08-30, Flatfile 1986.IA.36-5)